# Bakri Hmouda

Toronto, ON M2J 1L9 bakri.hmouda@gmail.com +1 437 473 2130

As a web developer with 1.5 years of experience gained through an intensive 8-month boot camp, I have honed my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various frameworks. In addition, I have over 16 years of experience in photography and photo editing using Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom. This extensive background has allowed me to bring a unique perspective and creative approach to my web development projects. I possess a strong attention to detail and a dedication to creating visually stunning, user-friendly, and efficient web applications. With my combined expertise in web development and photography, I am well-equipped to deliver exceptional results for any project.

## Work Experience

### **Web Developer**

Freelance Web Development - Tripoli August 2022 to Present

- Create front end web apps using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Nextjs, Angular, Astro, and Svelte-kit.
- Create back end apps using Node, Express, Laravel.
- Build e-commerce websites using Wordpress
- Design front end UI with Figma.

## **Photographer**

freelance photographer - Tripoli September 2018 to Present

- Digital Photography
- Digital image retouching [Adobe Photoshop, Adobe LightRoom, CaptureOne]
- Photography light setup

#### Photographer and Digital Image Retoucher

STAR MEDIA STUDIO - Tripoli June 2006 to September 2018

- Digital Photography
- Digital image retouching [Adobe Photoshop, Adobe LightRoom, CaptureOne]
- Photography light setup
- Graphic design [Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign]

#### Education

#### **Certificate in Web development**

CODI.tech - Tripoli

October 2021 to August 2022

## High school diploma in Accounting Tripoli

LYCÉE LIBANAIS - Tripoli

2007 to 2009

### Skills

- JavaScript
- CSS
- Git
- Web Development
- React
- APIs
- MongoDB
- Angular
- AJAX
- Node.js
- HTML5
- MySQL
- Bootstrap
- PHP
- User Interface (UI)
- Adobe Photoshop (10+ years)
- Adobe Lightroom (5 years)
- Adobe InDesign (2 years)
- Adobe Illustrator (2 years)

### Languages

- English Fluent
- Arabic Native
- French Beginner
- Turkish Beginner

#### Assessments

# Filing & organization — Highly Proficient

July 2023

Arranging and managing information or materials using a set of rules

Full results: Highly Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.